What's up?
What's going on, man?
Today's Thursday.
You know what that means, right?
It means that I'm lying.
Because it's actually Friday!
Are you excited?
I had to double-check halfway through.
I was like Thursday, then I looked at the computer.
Shit.
I said it wrong.
I can't believe it's Friday.
Oh, yeah.
Friday, my lord.
Are you all having a good day?
Great weather indeed.
Also in Denmark.
It's so hot outside.
I need to figure out some kind of solution for the heat that's coming this summer.
Otherwise, I'm gonna, you know, have more of those.
What do you call it?
Fever dreams, dreams.
Those were something else last year.
Man, I remember Minecraft.
That was just... I don't know.
That was weird during that time.
It's cold in Argentina.
Is that true?
Argentina sounds like a hot country.
I have no cooling socks, unfortunately.
I would love to.
Yeah, that would be cool.
A little air condition installed in each of my socks.
Now, that would be awesome.
Is it workers stay everywhere?
I don't know.
Well, yeah, you're right.
That is the first of May today.
So I guess in Denmark, it is abaidaness... stay.
Abaidaness... I forget the word for it.
But yeah, people are probably out drinking today.
Not me, though.
I'm here gaming.
Yep.
I'm not actually sure what it is.
It's just an excuse in Denmark to go drink, pretty much.
That's all I know.
I've already played a little bit of Rimworld, but less than three hours or so.
It was a little overwhelming and confusing.
But I want to try it again, because it was cool and it had good music.
Guys, check this out.
Finally, we have a substitute for the shitty backlog website, where you can't search for games.
People keep recommending the same games that are already on the list.
Is it just a preview?
It'll be up soon.
But check this out.
This is it.
It's the backlog.
And the best part?
You can search.
So, for example, let's say, I don't know, you want to watch or check whether or not I've played Subnautica, right?
It writes up and it's searching immediately.
Lightning fast, snappy responsive.
None of that, you know, animated bullshit.
It's just straight up working, okay?
And the best part?
There's even links to the vods.
Let's say you want to watch Minecraft, right?
Click on that.
Look at the seasons.
It's even counting up the total playtime.
I had no idea Season 2 was this long.
What the hell is that?
Look at that.
500 hours?
Or if you want to do it fast, you click here, you know, and you choose.
Isn't that amazing?
Oh yeah, and this one is 11 out of 10, of course.
Oh, and you can also, like, I don't know, you can click on these, you know, like, you can check what I've been playing in the past.
What's on my backlog?
What's on hold?
What I'm currently playing?
You know, kind of cool.
You can do that.
And there it is.
It's not up yet.
It's gonna be up soon.
Hell yeah.
What do you think of that, huh?
I'm using IGDB through Twitch.
Is this what you vibed between streams pretty much?
Yeah.
Claude, make an awesome website.
It's not that simple, but it's almost that simple nowadays.
I can't stand the fact that you can't search on backlogged.
This all stemmed from that, you know?
How come you can't search someone's backlog on backlogged?
Isn't that the whole point?
It's crazy.
I even voted on the roadmap on backlogged, you know?
But yeah, I guess it doesn't matter.
People don't want that feature, it seems.
It's very low down on the priorities.
What's up, Bobios-SJP?
Bobiospe?
I'm gonna call you Bobiospe.
Never catch your life, so feel blessed?
What the heck is going on?
I don't know.
It's hot outside.
It's Friday.
Man, I feel like getting drunk today.
Drunk Isaac, what do you think about that?
Is that a genius idea or a horrible idea?
Oh, definitely blood drunk.
You better believe it.
A genius?
I feel like that's gonna produce even more, you know, moments that piss you guys off.
But, you know, I feel like the more you guys get pissed off, the more entertained I am.
Not meaning that I get entertained by you being pissed off, it's just that the moments that piss you off usually entertain me a lot.
You know?
Okay, let me turn this down just a bit.
I'm ready to play some Isaac.
Isaac?
Where are you, Isaac?
What are you up to, Isaac?
Isaac, are you ready to play today?
Yes.
That's good.
Here we are.
Oh, we're gonna be doing things today because we finally did the challenge last time.
The challenge that had us beat for so long has now been stricken from the record, baby.
And it's time to move on to the solar system.
But not yet.
Not yet.
Also, isn't Suicide King a video game?
Isn't there a video game called Suicide King where you jump around or something?
Jump, jump, criss-cross.
Something like that, at least.
So I want to do a couple things today.
We unlocked a new character.
I want to play with Bethany again, and I also want to do speedruns on Azazel.
I know, I know, Azazel.
Give me a break, okay?
I love the guy.
And we're also gonna go step with, you guessed it, Magdalene.
So a little bit less random today, but more like forced going to a new character if I fuck up on one character that I didn't random.
Okay, so that we still get some variety.
I think we should start off with Azazel.
That's right.
It's the classic.
We're doing it.
Speedrun.
Okay.
Well, hold on, hold on.
I need to.
Okay, adjusted.
Right.
Shirts off.
Pants off.
Keyboard rotated.
90 degrees.
There we go.
Let's go.
All right, pre-charge before we go in.
We're not gonna mess this one up.
Oh, I'm so locked in right now already.
I love gaming.
Why is gaming so fun?
It's the best part about life.
Remember in the past when people made fun of gamers?
Not anymore.
There we go.
Wait, what was that?
Oh, that was a pill.
Paramones.
That's cool.
Oh, wait, we were speedrunning.
Scatter bombs.
Bomb explosively.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Maybe I can afford to, you know, destroy some of these fires.
Oh, we also have this one.
But I gotta go fast.
Taking out the high priority targets first.
Beautiful.
Look at that.
That is so fast.
In fact, we're gonna have time left over, I think, to do all kinds of funny stuff on the way.
Are you done?
You're done.
What are you doing, son?
Okay.
Not falling for that.
Nice.
Speed.
Oh, we don't really need that, though.
We have so much already.
Moving on.
I think as long as we get treasure rooms and we do the shops, assuming we have money, then we're good.
Then we keep moving.
Okay, see, this right here, I definitely have time to do this a little bit.
Especially with Azazel.
Oh, man, nothing?
That's sad.
Good.
I feel so strong.
Okay, no more.
Move on.
Eradicated.
Oh, sick.
That's actually massive.
Let's go in here.
Now that we have money.
Oh, member card would be cool.
Let's see if we can save up for that.
We are in a timer, though.
Uh, yeah.
I don't know what this does, but let's just do it.
Okay.
Sweet.
I missed the room.
What do we got here?
No problem.
Alright, this speed right here is... I think I've never been this fast before in a run.
Like, this is just beautiful.
Okay, come on.
Careful now.
Sweet.
These are dangerous.
Not that dangerous.
And there's the boss.
Oh, this one's gonna be easy as Azazel.
We love it.
Oh, he almost got hit there.
Wait, he normally doesn't do that.
That's new.
Nice.
Yeah, that's cool.
Give me that.
We also have this.
Three?
That kills me!
Wait, what's the point of that?
That doesn't make any sense.
Useless.
Treasure room has not been found.
We go back.
We go here and then down.
No mistakes.
Precision.
Here.
Wow.
Oh god.
They are fast.
How would you even dodge that if you weren't Azazel?
I've loaded it up.
I'm wasting too much time here.
What's that?
Let's Isaac throw a poison bomb.
Okay, I mean, very underwhelming.
Not worth it to come back for this.
It is nice to throw bombs though.
We can check for secrets like that.
Oh, I thought I had two charges on it.
Moving on.
We should be ahead of the timer for sure.
Okay.
This way.
Yeah, hey!
I really should be killing these first.
Sir.
Okay.
You know what, I should use my bomb for stuff like this.
Nice!
Exactly what I needed.
I'm gonna blow this up and that.
Maybe it... Oh, the small ones don't blow up things, it seems.
Oh, look at this here.
Oh!
Nope!
Light them up.
Secret room.
Yeah, let's do it.
Oh, that's the one I've already been in.
Ah, fuck!
I didn't mean to step!
Too bad.
Dude.
Okay.
You know what, I'm happy about that.
Let go of the black hearts.
Now I feel free, you know?
I need a couple more red hearts, for sure.
Blow this guy up before he does any damage.
Ah, man.
I imagine...
or I'm trying to imagine what speedrunning the game for real looks like.
Like, if people...
No, actual speedrunners.
It's probably a lot faster than this.
We're gonna throw a bomb.
Oh my god!
How is it so good?
Plus
one health?
Soul heart, black heart?
That's an amazing item?
What?
Oh, don't jump down yet.
We have treasure room.
That is a crazy one.
Never seen that.
Well, now we're totally chilling.
Where are you?
There you are.
Okay.
That should be it.
You wanna dance?
That's for you.
Dude, this bomb is incredible.
Maybe one of the best actives.
Die, please.
Okay.
What's that?
Two of spades.
Oh yeah, that's cool.
Why not?
We still haven't found treasure room.
I think there's a secret here.
Shit.
I thought wrong.
Where's the door?
There should be a door on the left here.
Maybe I'm blind.
Oh, it's a secret room, I see.
Good night.
So satisfying when you kill the guy and his little minions that spawn with one attack.
Eraser?
No, I like this more.
Okay, we leave after this room.
I really shouldn't leave faster.
We don't have time.
It's not a proper speed run if I don't speed run.
Okay, go, go, go.
Boss is in the bottom right.
Let's go.
Fast, fast, fast.
Let's see if we're ahead.
We are.
As long as we keep this up, we're good, right?
I don't think it matters how far ahead we are.
I will do this though, just because I can.
Worth.
Oh shit.
Faster, mom.
Good, move.
Oh, that evil fire.
40 damage?
Yeah, why not?
I think I understand how to fight these guys now, like properly.
You bait one attack and then you just move.
That's pretty much it.
I could use a bit more damage.
This room was taken forever.
Can't destroy poops.
No time.
Nice.
Dude, so far, so good.
Holy.
I'm doing well.
This is for you.
Shit.
How did that miss so badly?
I was trying to show off.
They ruined it.
What is that?
Gemini?
Uh, right.
Okay.
I take it.
We got money.
Uh, blood bag.
Oh, definitely.
Definitely.
I could even have rerolled actually.
What if I rerolled now?
Oh, no way.
I need one more coin.
We can definitely get more coins.
Die!
I was being greedy.
My bad.
Okay, go back.
Let me see what that item was.
Uh, Beelzebub.
Uh, I don't like that.
Shit.
I want to reroll one more time, you know?
Uno mas.
You bastard.
War is coming.
Hey, you like bombs?
Oh, wait, that did a... What?
Why did those spawn?
Interesting.
Man, Gemini is helping.
Okay, we got that one.
That's cool.
Move on.
I need to, uh, waste more money on the reroll.
Give me that.
I know this is not very good for speed run.
No!
Okay, fine.
I'll take it.
I take it and I move on.
Ow!
It's all part of the process.
It's mom time?
Dude, already.
It's already mom time.
This has to be my fastest run so far.
I'm losing too much HP here.
What the...
Good night!
Oh, I can't see anything.
No map.
Uh, we also had a door with some keys there.
I'm taking that.
Sick.
Oh,
good.
What's that?
Healing?
That's closed?
Sick.
Man, bombs are super good for speed running.
What's that?
Wishbone?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
That's cool.
We like it.
Hell, there's a resource!
It's okay.
Oh wait, there's more doors.
Go, go, go.
Oh, what is this room?
No problem.
Nothing there.
Oh man, where's the... where's the boss?
Oh shit.
Oh, you bastard.
Okay.
Here we go.
Did I miss with that bomb?
That's crazy.
I can't believe that.
I should have just gone for the bomb immediately.
Good.
Kill that guy.
Did she just kill her own minion?
That's awesome.
There we go.
Nice.
Give me that one.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
But I don't have a lot of HP.
It's okay.
We go for it.
Is that what I think it is?
Uh, wait, how do I see it again?
Oh yeah, shift.
No, wait, I thought that was pyromaniac.
Horror of Babylon.
That's pretty good.
Placenta.
Mom's lip.
I mean, range is actually super good for me and I don't have a lot of it right now.
I think I may need this.
And I need the red heart.
I really wanted to take the top left one, but I gotta take the range, man.
Okay, wish me luck here.
Oh god, oh god.
Oh my god, I'm gonna die here.
Dude, like I'm getting hit from all kinds of shit all the time.
Okay.
Stay behind the goddamn wall.
Holy shit.
I'm dead.
There's no way I've survived this.
There's, there's too much.
It's, it's too much.
Oh, where are you going?
Where are you going?
Okay, he's dead.
He's dead.
Give me some HP.
Where are you?
There you are.
Hoish.
Duh.
There you are.
Did we get some HP?
Throw.
What?
I don't know how I died, but okay.
Okay, one more time.
One more time on this.
Man, that was tough as hell.
Lost way too much HP in the beginning there.
Give me that.
Good warm up, though.
Like, that was probably the fastest run I've had so far.
We can make it faster.
Dude, these guys are the worst.
Okay, that's nice.
Where's the treasure?
Show me the treasure.
Uh, nope.
I didn't have that much damage anyway, that last run there.
It felt terrible to be at that stage without a lot of damage, you know?
Okay.
Uh, I can't afford any of this.
We'd love to get the blue heart, though.
Treasure room.
Okay, there's also a book room.
I mean, re-rolling something I don't know what is, is useless.
Check this out.
These are question marks, but we are gonna know what it is.
Monster manual.
The Bible!
Hey, sick!
We probably don't need it too much, but, you know, I mean, we already have flying and mom is not gonna be that much of a problem, but, you know.
Okay, that was my best bet at the secret room.
Move on.
Maybe I'll do angels, actually.
Because we didn't get a, uh, devil room anyway.
Full angel?
Since we have the Bible, you know, good cosplaying, or larping, whatever you want to call it.
Oh, shit, I don't have a key.
Uh, well, that's unfortunate.
Okay, move, move, move.
There we go.
That's what I needed.
Uh, sure.
Scapegoat is good.
Oh, that was money.
Totally worth destroying these poofs in passing, you know.
I'll eat that.
Oh, that was not great.
Fuck.
Wait, what did that do?
It damaged me, right?
That's it?
I think it removed the black heart.
Black heart's temporary, anyway.
Uh, can't go that way.
Look at him going for the scapegoat.
Die!
Terrible.
I'm trying to look for, uh, what do you call it, tinted rocks at the same time, but I'm not having any success.
Go on.
Let's try the Bible against Stephen, see what happens.
I sentenced you to Christianity, or whatever.
I mean, as long as the scapegoat is taking care of these guys, then I'm just chilling.
Oi!
Oh, man.
Okay, we got damage now.
Not taking a deal, I can guarantee you that.
Okay, now we're pretty much Judas, but much better than Judas, you know.
Oh, he killed himself.
Uh, we can do it down here.
Oh, wait, I thought that was an enemy.
It's my friend.
Not going in there.
I need treasure room and I need to get out.
That's the plan.
Again, I don't need the belts.
I have speed.
Wait, this opened now.
I don't know why, but it did.
Okay.
Totally worth.
Sick.
That was clean.
The extra damage, I can totally feel it.
Man, didn't get a good heart.
Man,
I am so happy this wasn't laser.
What's happened?
Oh.
Oh, no, I have no HP.
We got to go heal.
Grab this.
We're going to need to find a treasure room, though, like before we do anything.
There it is.
Good.
What's that one?
That's good.
I like it.
So I don't think this one reveals secret rooms, though.
Oh, wait, we have money.
Go, go, go.
Okay,
let me see here.
I think I want...
It's too risky.
There's nothing in here.
I don't want any of that.
Mega fatty.
I sentence you to Christianity.
Oh, you're petrified, are you?
Oh, actually pulled me into him.
Okay, I take that.
You take this, we leave.
Do the black.
My bad.
Speed.
What's that?
Continuum.
Tears pass through walls and obstacles.
Tears that travel off the... Oh, I like it.
So how's that?
Is that?
Yeah, okay, okay, I need more range.
More range is needed.
Let me also see here exactly.
More range is fantastic, of course.
We like that a lot.
Oh, nice.
The virus.
Oh, didn't even see that guy on the left.
Yo, okay, okay.
Okay, dude.
This way, there's an arcade here.
Nice.
That's fine.
I can't see what that is.
Shit.
It's not fine, actually.
The spiders.
Nice.
What was that jump across the screen?
That was crazy.
The longest jump I've ever seen.
Okay.
No, that's closed.
Huge.
The door has opened.
Point here.
Show me the good stuff.
What's that?
Sharp pluck.
Using uncharged item will exchange half a red heart for missing charge.
No, no.
Hate it.
Horrible.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going in.
I'm going to try the Bible on him.
Just for kicks.
Oh, I like that.
I like that.
Angel!
I was about to say, are we going to get an angel?
What do we got?
Uh, I don't know what that is.
This one is not super exciting.
So I'm taking this.
Circle of protection.
Protect me from myself.
Creates a ring around Isaac that has a chance to reflect enemy projectiles.
Enemies inside the ring take Isaac's damage once per second.
Whoa!
That sounds really good.
I like it.
Dude, I'm going to kill this guy.
Stay mad.
I wonder if I can see a difference between diagonal and non-diagonal lasers from him.
Ah, shit.
Ow!
Stop that.
Okay.
We got a piece of a key.
We have found everything we needed, so we move on!
Good run so far.
We're ahead of the timer.
Everything is going according to plan.
Double whammy!
Look at me optimizing, collecting coins.
The formium is done.
That's how much speed I have.
What?
What hit me?
Damn.
Oh, wait.
Are we curse of the labyrinth or something?
I think we are.
Okay, I need to pull myself together.
This is not great.
Let's go get that heart.
Let's see here.
Ah, it's nice.
Okay, that's good.
I like that.
Ah, I don't like it.
The game giveth, the game taketh away.
Show yourself.
We have 30 coins.
Okay, we need a proper shop now.
Yeah, everything is messed up.
The map is confusing.
Destroy these.
Useless.
Ah, yeah.
Oh, wait.
You're the battery guy, right?
Let me just confirm that.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, shit.
Ah, I guess we go for it.
Monstro.
Oh, I forgot he did that.
I thought he was doing something else.
Are we angeling?
No angel.
That's really good, though.
I need my treasure room.
I know we're speedrunning, but ah.
We gotta be able to find it fast, right?
Can't be that much left.
Also, we can see rooms ahead here.
Uh, blow that up.
Dammit.
Also, I saw a secret room.
Right there.
That'll be good.
Uh, it's not good.
I'm gonna blow it up.
Running out of bombs here.
That's amazing!
Okay.
We're not taking any more pills now.
We are gonna quit while ahead.
In fact, that feels so good, we're gonna move on.
Now it's mom time, and we are really far ahead of the circle.
Or, uh, timer, I mean.
Circular time.
Whoa!
Yes!
Health red heart applies charm!
Charm and damage in close range.
I am immune to close range right now.
Oh, that's cool.
That's amazing!
Charm is one of my favorite things.
Oh!
Okay.
Uh, secret room has been indicated.
Show you thyself.
Okay, over here.
What's this?
Oh, I have no bombs!
Oh crap, cake!
Plenty of money, though.
Would like a couple more tiers so I can charge up faster.
There's the bomb I needed.
Let's go to the room over here first.
Optimize our path.
Yeah!
That's so good!
Dude, I am ultimate protection man right now.
Nothing can get close to me.
This is gonna help out so much.
Bless RNGesus.
This is what happens to people who carry the Bible, is all I'm saying, you know?
And again, I did murder an angel on the way here.
But it's fine.
That happens, you know?
I can't really control that.
The ladder?
I don't like that.
That's boring.
This guy's camouflaged!
That was so satisfying.
Oh yeah.
Oh!
Close one.
What is that chest even like?
It's a weird one.
You can just keep opening it.
Open!
Oh, I don't have any keys!
Fuck!
I just used it on that stupid brick!
That's horrible.
Goodnight, mom!
Nice knowing ya!
We even got angels!
I don't know what that is.
That's really good, but what is this?
Immaculate heart, Halo of Tears.
Damage?
Nice.
Health?
Heels or red hearts?
Chance to fire additional spectral tears that orbit around Isaac?
Wow!
Is that gonna work with my laser?
Two out of three on Seraphim.
I'm gonna blow these fools up, dude.
One at a time.
Let's calm down here a little bit, you know?
Yeah, walk into that.
That's good.
Walk into the laser.
I mean, the fire.
Goodnight.
Key piece one.
Let me see here.
Key piece two.
But there was also another key.
I wanna get that other key.
Are you gonna reveal the other key to me?
Cool.
Come on, then.
No problem.
Nothing from you, huh?
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Can I grab that?
Nice.
Oh, we're gonna grab this.
We're gonna go in here.
Here we go.
Wait, why is it looking like this?
This is a small room.
Leo, he can break things, or...
the hourglass.
I... I... I... I like this.
We're gonna save the Bible.
We're gonna stay religious.
Okay, you bastard.
You're dead.
Oh, that was a... Right.
I can't walk into the TNT barrels.
Not with the Leo.
I'm just blow those up so I don't do that.
Seems good.
Get rid of all the hazards.
Okay.
Now we gotta focus.
No messing up now.
Damage is good this time around.
I'm gonna puke.
And you're dead.
Whoa.
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi.
I didn't mean to place that bomb, that was a mistake.
Yeah, the damage this time around is so much better.
That sci-fi is helping a lot.
It's actually incredible.
That's Steven.
He's gonna explode into a million pieces.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there it is.
Why didn't you get stunned by that?
You were supposed to get stunned by that, son.
Parts for me in case I need it later.
So hectic.
Dude, this is so much fun!
I love this!
I wanna do this every run.
I mean, as long as you have skill, you can get a free item, right?
Actually, more than one, I guess.
Ah, shit.
He's done.
Next.
Come on, no more opaque.
What's that up there?
Oh, it's you.
Look out, you were there.
I'm losing a bit of HP here.
Where's the other one?
I mean, they can charge across.
That's cool.
Man, the sci-fi is helping so much.
Oh, wait, that's mine.
I thought the Gemini was an enemy.
Your kids are dead!
What you gonna do about it?
You gonna die.
Ah, that was really fake.
This guy needs to die, actually.
He's a menace.
Wait, I have two Geminis.
Why is that?
I should be using my charm, I think, more.
That means I gotta get close.
Man, this floor is looking like a Jackson Pollock painting right now.
It's beautiful.
What the hell is that?
Little IEDs.
Okay.
15 out of 15.
Get the little guys out of here first.
Those are the most annoying.
What happened?
We got slowed down, I think?
Or did everything get slowed down?
I'm not sure.
Boy, oh my god.
That's tough to dodge.
There we go!
Anti-gravity!
Tears will hover in place while pressing attack button.
Releasing attack button will shoot all hovering tears off in the direction they were fired in.
Uh...
I don't know if that sounds good with me.
Oh wait, what is this shit?
That's horrible!
What the hell is that?
Huh?
Get this shit off of me!
Oh my god, that is terrible!
What is that?
Well, that's just...
terrible!
That just ruined everything!
How am I even gonna play the game?
Oh no, it's so bad!
Why is this an item?
This is like a curse!
I literally can't kill anything!
This is...
We gotta make use of the circle we have, that's the only way.
We getting close?
Because my attack is now useless.
Unless I find something else that overrides it.
Kill each other.
Yeah.
Okay, not gonna go in there.
There's a secret room here.
Uh, blow that up.
Ah shit, whatever.
Wait, I didn't take damage from those!
Ah!
Okay.
So what do I do with this key that I have right here?
Where do I use that?
I can't believe this item.
I think it may be... I can't even think when it would be good.
Like, if you have normal tiers, maybe?
But that still sounds terrible.
Like...
I wanna drop the item.
Just... proximity kill them.
Why not?
Kill each other.
What's that?
The tower?
The tower.
Oh yeah, right.
Good.
Secret down there.
They killed each other.
Wait, what?
Oh yeah.
Give me something that overrides my item, please!
Look at this room.
That's kinda cool.
I like that room.
I'm not damaging them?
Okay.
Maybe I can do that.
Nice.
I'm not gonna be able to kill anything.
Like, this is the problem now.
The bloat!
What am I... Oh, these guys.
I didn't see them.
Good.
I am very low HP here.
Oh no.
Do we have any healing?
Not really.
Move on.
Okay, we got secret and treasures.
Wow.
I mean, money we have.
The hangman is useless.
Okay, okay.
As long as enemies are big, then I'm happy.
Easy to hit.
This room I do not understand.
This is just such a weird room.
No, Scotland.
Oh, booger, that's good.
That's some damage at least.
I mean, it's going okay here.
It is a disaster, but you know.
All things considered.
I'll take that.
Dead end.
So it's going to be...
Who we fighting next?
It lives.
Okay, that's good.
I like that.
Oh, that's nice.
More healing.
That's wonderful.
I'm getting better at this item, though.
Secret discovered.
I could blow it up, I guess.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, we're not done.
We got the Bible.
Good night!
Sweet!
Okay, so we can do this again if we want to.
Let's do it again.
I feel...
Oh, what?
That's different.
Okay.
Oh, that was an easy room.
Ah, yeah, okay.
Already paying off!
Bookworm, but how does that work with me?
Oh, wait, there was a pill.
Pretty nice!
More flies!
Love my flies!
Damage, damage, damage.
Oh, that opened!
Not gonna question why.
Accept it.
Okay, I got no keys.
Let's go here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's scary.
That was a tough room.
It's I'm so good at making really good decisions.
How do I know?
Exhibit one.
Look at the screen.
Okay, this is getting a little risky.
Yeah, everyone dies now.
Hey, hey, hey!
Kill him.
Okay.
Oh, wait, they're my friends.
Come with me, friends.
We got black poop in here.
Check out this guy.
What we're gonna do, we're gonna attack him once until he collapses and then we do a big one.
Oh, never mind.
Bombs are helping.
Bombs are good.
I did lose a lot of my blue hearts, though.
It is what it is.
Binky.
Soulheart size down.
I like it.
Harder to hit.
I'm a tiny little fast demon.
Okay, I'm good here.
Let's move on.
Maybe I'll go for angels now.
But wait, I already took a deal.
So can I even?
Am I completely locked out of that now or can I earn some goodwill?
Let's go find out.
Dude, this character is actually kind of sick.
Good.
Aha!
I take those.
Ooh, that one is, uh, yo.
I love that one.
That one is so much fun.
So it's every room now, right?
Oh, wait a minute.
It's consumed.
Oh, wait, I thought I had it once per floor.
Oh, man.
Fuck.
Oh, I learned my lesson though.
Now we know that.
I guess it would be a little crazy, right?
If it was for every floor.
Okay.
This is amazing.
I love the mega bomb.
So good.
Okay, let's go south.
Everything just dies.
I wonder if this is gonna one shot a boss or something.
Where's the secret?
There it is.
Oh, I didn't even have a chance to do anything in here.
I guess this is the downside.
You want to go to shops first, you know, before you do this.
Okay, these guys are not bothered at all.
That's cool.
Oh, this is so good.
Ah, feels nice.
Okay, there was nothing else over here.
This was closed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, we got decent HP out of this.
Haga, I mean, do we really need to destroy more things?
That is the question right now.
Have we not done enough damage?
Shit.
Oh, nice.
Not that it matters.
Whoa.
I can't see shit anyway.
Nice.
Oh, I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
It just happened.
Less shot speed?
I mean, I guess my damage must scale with these guys, right?
Otherwise, it would be pretty sad.
So totally worth.
It actually just kills everyone.
That's crazy.
Where am I supposed to go?
Where's the boss?
I forgot.
Did I even clear everything?
I think I did clear that.
Yeah, since there's no explosions here, it means I've been here, right?
I could go in here.
Gopey's tail?
Sure.
Why not?
Not super thrilled about that, but it's okay.
Do I want to buy?
Oh, I could buy this.
Yeah, not bad.
Ah, here we go.
I didn't even find the boss.
Shit.
Let's see how much damage this is going to do to the boss.
What the fuck?
Bro, the bomb is broken?
Legit just broken?
What the fuck?
Oh, I need that again.
I need that bomb again.
Imagine using that on like the latest stage you can.
Damn, that sounds good.
I'm so used to everything just dying.
It's sad that it doesn't anymore.
Bring it on then.
Secrets.
Yeah, baby.
Amazing.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Careful now.
I can't see where they are.
Okay, this is going to kill him.
Hopefully.
We got worms inbound.
Come on.
Good enough.
Didn't even kill him.
Hey, I've got some keys for you.
Not too many, though.
Okay.
Oh, thanks, brother.
Have a bomb.
You suck.
That's what taking five of my coins or keys.
Oh, God.
Turns into an evil bastard.
Nice.
That's also not the blue heart up north, in case we need one more.
Dude, I actually kind of like that effect with the bombs.
Good stuff.
Uh-oh.
They're charmed.
Wait.
Oh, they're my friends.
Right.
True.
Okay, kill them.
They're my friends.
Oh, shit.
Are you going to blow this up?
Battery pack, full of recharges, the hell.
Battery pickups.
I don't like that.
This one is kind of good.
But, man, this is not very cool, all of this.
Very boring.
I don't like any of it.
Maybe key.
I'll take a key.
I mean, whatever.
Maybe I'll come back for these batteries.
Got to spend the money, right?
Just break it all.
Kill them.
Bro, these bombs are useless?
Help me, man.
What am I paying you for?
Game bombs?
I like this.
That's huge.
Not really.
Fly, buddies.
Love amassing an army here.
Hey, I got bombs for you.
I got plenty.
Give me an item.
A good item.
Okay.
I mean, it's not bad, but what about an item?
Okay, I'm not going to give you bombs anytime soon now.
I need some for myself.
Come on.
One more.
Fine.
I'll see you later.
Cheers.
I don't think that does anything for me.
I think damage is one of the few stats that affect me.
Let's go.
Oh, thank you for that.
Thank you.
Dude, my little guys are shooting so many.
That is so good.
Look at the damage output of that.
I barely have to do anything.
I'm just chilling back here.
What the hell?
Oh, they're spiders.
What the...
Okay, that was confusing as hell.
That's useless for me, but that's okay.
That is what it is.
What is dakas?
Removes curses and... Oh, that's cool.
Money!
That should be good for me.
Or activate a demon form that grants damage and speed up when hot.
Oh, that could be pretty good.
That could be really good, actually.
In fact, I could take this and that.
That leaves me with one heart.
Yeah, wait, we didn't turn into a demon.
What was it again?
Uh... oh, half a red heart or less.
Okay, shit.
Do we have a blood donation?
Maybe, actually.
Let's go back and check.
Somewhere, there's gotta be.
Also, let's blow some shit up.
Do we have, like, a arcade here?
I don't think so.
Wait, we have a blue heart we can go grab.
We're gonna lose half a blue heart for this, but that's fine.
Still a net positive.
Let's just take a peek in here.
I may like that more.
No, I like this.
If we get a shitty curse, could be nice.
How am I gonna get rid of that half a heart?
Shit.
Maybe we find a blood donation machine.
It's time for mom.
I'm ready.
I'm so ready.
I'm gonna throw away a fart bomb in her face.
It's gonna be glorious.
They can jump in here.
Yeah, careful, careful.
Okay, got some healing.
Oh, no, this is gonna be really tough.
He's gonna see me now, and then I go in.
Nice.
Oh, crap.
Get him.
Hey, well, there it is.
Hey, beautiful.
Let's see if I notice a difference in damage now.
Oh, this guy was also here, I guess, in case I wanted to utilize him.
Oh, that's unfair, you bastard.
Shit's not going well.
I can't be losing all this HP.
What?
Oh.
Am I scaling with damage?
I think so.
I think I do more damage now.
I shouldn't have healed up.
I messed up.
Get that damage in.
Okay, this should be good.
Oh, man.
Oh, thanks.
I'm in trouble.
Do I want this?
Maybe.
Oh, what?
I'm rich.
Oh, yes.
What have we got?
PhD?
It's nice.
And a mystery gift.
Yeah.
Ah.
What I mean.
Better than nothing.
Worst pill ever.
Maybe I'll buy this.
Yeah, that was, yeah.
Okay.
Not great.
I am just severely lacking damage.
I think I may have thrown this run.
At this point, it's not looking good.
I got bombs I can throw.
That's my saving grace.
Yeah, you like that?
The flies are my friends.
Is mom's foot even gonna stomp down here?
I wonder.
Wait, I'm gonna... Oh, wait.
No, I thought it was the one that destroyed fucking rocks.
Damn it.
Oh, man.
She destroyed the rocks.
Actually, huge with the bombs.
Yeah.
Bombs from heaven.
Beautiful.
We got range.
That's useless for me, but maybe two out of three on Yes, Mother, could come in handy later.
Or something.
I don't recall what it does, but, you know, maybe it can come handy.
Oh,
maybe worth.
I'm taking a shot at this.
I'm taking a shot.
I could also try this one.
That takes me to three out of three on Guppy.
I don't recall what that does.
Wait, a pentagram.
I'm gonna try it.
Guppy.
I don't know what it did, but we now have an extra heart or life.
This may have been a mistake.
I don't know.
One and a half heart.
I think we're dead.
This is not good.
We need a miracle, pretty much.
If I don't do it this run, I will throw out the leftover tacos, and I shall not be enjoying those tonight.
I'm kidding.
We're not going to put that on the line.
That's too much.
Oh, that guy really needs to die.
Yeah, what do I even do?
Oh, there we go.
That's nice.
Saved by the bell.
Tears up, it's not gonna matter.
I am so dead.
We got tiles!
That means I'm dead!
Yeah.
Oh wait, we're alive.
I forgot we had this.
How am I gonna win here?
I can't.
We gotta bomb him.
That a heart?
That is a heart.
Oh, I can't grab it though!
I have no red hearts!
Run into it!
I'm so done.
I am so done.
Oh my god.
How?
How did I do that?
Incredible!
Die!
We're back!
This room is gonna be the end of me!
One down.
Two down.
We use the red one.
Blue, red.
Blue.
Kill him!
Good.
He's down, he's down.
Focus, focus.
We missed our shot.
Launch window, missed.
Solar system is not great in here.
Come on, come on.
Ah, why did you have to stand still, you bastard?
Okay, we did some good damage there.
We go around.
Red fly!
Nice!
Blue, red.
Kill him.
Yeah.
Huge.
Focus up.
The blue is very low HP, it has to be.
There we go!
Getting closer.
Kill him!
Fuck!
Yeah!
Man!
I'm in danger!
Yeah, I knew you were gonna do that.
Bastard.
That's cool, that's cool!
Nice.
Wait for it.
Huge.
Just stand here, stand here.
We're fine.
We can do it.
Okay, he's gonna be over here.
That means I'm gonna be here.
You're gonna be there.
That means I'm here.
Okay.
That's rough.
You die.
One is gone, one is gone.
And he's gonna calm down now?
There we go.
Fuck you!
Okay.
Uh-oh, what's this now?
Yeah!
Oh no, I hate it.
Are they shooting at me?
If they're not, I can just chill.
They're not shooting.
Wait, one of them is.
Run away!
Yeah, you can't reach me.
You cannot reach me.
He can shoot me.
Let me get out.
Huge.
Where art thou?
Oh god.
One down.
Why is everything suddenly so freaking scary?
This run went from, oh, we're totally breezing, to wow, holding on to everything I can for dear life.
What happened?
You can't reach... I thought you couldn't reach me!
Bump.
Okay, I'm gonna blow this guy up.
Fuck him.
Totally worth.
I'm being taunted.
He's down.
Holy.
Okay.
How about some blue hearts, please?
I mean, yeah.
How are we still alive?
I don't understand.
I have no safe spots now.
It's all over.
Oh, nice.
Not nice.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, beautiful.
Oh, I can't believe we're still going.
This is the weirdest run of all time.
Mistakes were made.
Wow.
I mean, I'm just glad to start over.
I gotta be honest with you.
That was freaking torturous.
Absolute torture to play that.
I think we need something extra on this character to make it to the end.
I don't know what, but some kind of alternate way of dealing damage than these flies.
Because shit ain't cutting it.
Die shard.
That can come in handy.
The start is good.
We do good damage at the start, but then it just goes to shit, you know?
No keys for me.
I'll be back for that.
Oh, no.
School bag.
And this one...
Not that I can afford it.
I stay in the center.
Okay, I was afraid you were gonna do the green poop.
We can't lose any HP.
Also, no deals.
Somehow I just knew it was gonna go to shit when I took the deals, you know?
We only do angels.
Angels are good.
Oh God, you're fast.
Oh!
Bastard!
Nice!
Rain shot... I mean, okay.
I don't know which one... which stats are good for me.
This is my problem.
I don't even think damage is good for me, honestly.
The only thing I know that's good is survival.
Survivability.
That's what I need, you know?
Oh, hell no.
Unless...
Nice!
I got it.
I'm gonna hide in the center.
They can't get to me.
They don't jump, right?
I hope not.
Didn't give me any stats.
Oh wait, this is not bad, is it?
Oh, I thought it was the one that gave me stats.
I should have done that.
Because what if we find a...
Oh wait, there's no treasure rooms.
Huh.
Right.
Nevermind.
We're chilling.
Ah, no way.
I mean, not bad.
Oh, I need this.
Can't forget it.
This is gonna be tough.
This room is terrible for me.
I'm actually kinda glad that happened.
Fuck him.
Okay.
Widow!
Just keep running around right now.
He's gonna keep jumping.
It's tough to get in there.
Oh god.
Jesus.
Man, this pause is tough to deal with.
That's good.
That's a stat I can get behind.
Unfortunately, it wasn't an HP up.
Ugh.
But, you know.
So the shop, we can go check that out.
No, we can't.
I ain't got a key cap.
I need at least three more HP up.
Then I'm comfortable.
Then I think we can take this all the way to the win.
That is like my win condition, I think.
Broken syringe?
Chancing in a random syringe?
Why not?
Then again, champions.
Let's go with that.
They could drop the items that I've been desperately needing, right?
Oh, nice.
That's a good amount of healing.
Careful then, careful.
Oh man.
Man, hitting with the red fly is so incredibly hard.
I wish it would stand still, you know?
I need the item that does that.
Actually, that would be a huge item.
I mean, I like that.
Oh, I really want to bomb this, actually.
Sick.
Nice.
Hey, here we go.
The Empress.
What's that?
AWAS.
Oh, I like AWAS.
We're going to look for floor decoration.
This could be the break we've been waiting for.
I'm playing very not good right now.
I admit it.
Aww, these damn spiders.
My worst nightmare is the orbital guy.
I need to get told.
No, wait, that's the flies, right?
That's not spiders.
I need to heal up first.
Okay, so let's look for floor decorations here.
This could be one, but I'm not entirely sold on it.
Ah, man.
Maybe this one, for sure, though.
AWAS.
Yeah, nice.
Okay, so what do we got?
What is that?
Oh, that's massive!
Survival!
Polydactily!
I was holding two cards, pills, or runes.
Oh, wait, I can... How do I get there?
Huh?
How do I get in there?
Oh, that's weird.
I think I may need some other ability there.
Bombs for me.
Actually.
I kind of enjoy destroying shrooms.
Yeah, I like it.
The Empress gives me damage, but I don't think it matters on this character.
Here they come.
Max range.
Yeah, come this way.
There we go, and then go the other way.
The other way now, the other way now.
Oh, man.
Fuck.
Oh, it's so awkward.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There we go.
Okay, what do we have left?
Shop, and a boss.
Oh, I can stay safe in the center.
That's a relief.
Good stuff.
Oi, oi, oi.
Red fly is doing so good damage.
I got 14 coins.
I can definitely go on a spending spree.
Wow.
Man, this challenge is probably the hardest challenge so far.
If you think about all the other attempts I've made on this in the past as well, you know.
Oh, shit.
Oh, thanks.
I'm gonna blow this up, too.
Shop first.
Boco bombs.
Bosses.
Oh, that one.
Fo' sho, baby.
This better be good.
I get to have a choice now.
Let the red fly damage him.
It is risky.
Ah, yeah, it's too risky, it's too risky.
We use the blue one.
Careful.
It's gonna spawn another one soon.
Yeah, there it is.
I'm gonna wait for him to jump at me.
Bomb for you.
Lovely.
He didn't die from that.
Kill him.
Oh, man.
Okay.
Plus one health.
I am very tempted.
Ah, but all these stats don't matter to me.
But I guess it's better than the other guy.
Yeah.
Give me that one.
Okay.
Moving on.
I'm gonna keep destroying mushrooms in case we find more mushrooms.
Or to go for the three out of three.
I had to do it.
This room is a killer.
All right, wake up, wake up.
I can't believe I did that without losing any HP.
That must have been something else to watch, considering the fact that I always either die or lose half my HP in that room.
It was more luck than anything else.
Kill him.
That's a scary one.
I'm not sure what it does.
It takes away my hearts.
Okay, cool.
And then it spawns more hearts.
Oh, I
really want to bomb this.
Look at this.
Feels so good.
These guys are my friends.
I've been missing friends in this playthrough here.
I haven't seen a lot of them.
More friends.
Join my army.
Kill them all.
Go for it.
I believe in you.
Can you stop damaging the guy there, please?
There we go.
Very nice.
How did that hit me, man?
I thought I got out of there.
There.
Pause is here.
I'm going for it.
With all these minions, for sure.
Guys, you can attack him.
It's okay.
We're going to get two options now.
A box or a soul heart.
Red heart, key bomb, coin, pill, card.
Man, I don't like any of these options.
It's terrible.
I guess I can work on Yes Mother on this one.
And I get a blue heart, so it's better than nothing.
Let's go.
Okay, this way.
Oh!
I'm scared of this dude right here.
I don't like that he's blue.
Tomatoes.
Nice!
Man, that is so huge.
Finding stuff like that in a chest is incredible.
I also missed something behind a rock there.
The hell is that?
Equality?
Right?
It's a large fire rate increase when collected coins, bombs and keys are all equal in number.
I mean... No.
It doesn't even matter for me.
So why would I take that?
I need to shoot the boop.
That's what I need.
That would be insane.
I need a good active, you know?
Maybe the fart that charms enemies.
Oh, that would be nice.
Something like that.
And then I'm cooking.
Not bad.
Ah, we're not done.
I wonder if stepping could be worth it in one of these runs.
If I end up with a lot of red hearts, you know?
A chance of finding... Hey!
Definitely.
It's only 3% though.
What are those?
Whoa, they're fast.
Dude!
Okay, so they go across.
No, no, keep the other one on.
Dude, how do I deal with these fuckers?
Stop picking that up.
One down.
Huge stuff.
Nice.
There's more.
Oh, you fucking asshole.
Trying to ruin my run.
And succeeding.
Uh, maybe I do a hot delivery here.
Check it out.
We're gonna do this.
Wait, how did I get hit?
Oh, there's a fly.
That's for you.
That's for you!
Enjoy that.
Come at me.
Blue heart me.
It's looking like a tough run.
You know what?
Why not?
I have some healing.
I got one there and one in the shop.
Actually, there's two here.
Oh, that's sick.
I can go in here.
Yeah!
Mom's foot and what's the other one?
No.
Not worth it.
Oh, I hate the big rooms.
The big rooms are really tough when you're the solar system.
I wish I was the sun.
Another pill.
Useless for me.
I could look for blue hearts.
I hate when that happens.
Blow that up and this one too.
One more, one more.
Ah, damn.
I need every help I can get.
I have gone everywhere except the boss.
That's kind of crazy.
Oh, thanks buddies.
Here we go.
Loki!
Oh, we got the dudes.
I really need to be patient here.
He's my friend.
Yeah, you can spawn those if you want.
That's cool.
Yeah!
Spawn some more.
Loma!
Yes!
Good boy.
Not bad.
Oh, I see HP right there.
I see HP.
The other one is, yeah, that's useless.
This one for sure.
Absolutely.
Not bad.
Guys, I think we have reached the critical threshold.
We have a good amount of hearts.
This is the run.
Now, ideally, we should find some kind of active item that does damage.
If we can find that, then we're good.
It's looking really good.
What's that one?
Watch battery.
Increased chains of little battery spawning.
And what else?
Nah, I don't want room rewards.
I want my eternal hearts.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah, you're a real piece of shit.
I get it.
Now we wait.
That's not happening.
Not unless I find a bunch of hearts.
Why can't I find one of those rooms that spawn like 10,000 red hearts right now?
That's what I mean.
That was somehow clean.
We got a treasure room as well.
Or not a treasure room, but a chest room.
Can I damage these guys?
Oh, it's the other ones that need the damage.
I see.
Makes sense.
What was that just now?
Was that a blue fly absorbing the hit?
That gave zero fucks.
And look at that!
An eternal heart!
We are not gonna forget that one.
We're coming back for it.
Mark my words.
We'll leave no eternal heart behind.
I don't think I've ever done that, actually.
Maybe once.
But they're just so important, you know?
You don't really forget that.
Oh, man.
Yeah, good.
No, thanks.
Let's look for the boss.
I'm rich.
Oh, no, there's no item.
Maybe I can find an item.
Hey, dude, check this out.
Oh, shit, nice.
Come here.
Okay, then.
Be that way.
Well, now we got coins.
Even more coins.
What am I gonna spend it on?
Give me a beggar.
Yeah, this one's gonna be...
I'm gonna be in this room for 10 years.
I can tell you right now.
One down.
Good configuration.
Nice!
I'm so glad.
Okay, we have a boss here.
I'm doing it.
And then we take eternal, and then after that, we go.
Hit her with the red fly, if we can.
Oh, that was a fast secondary attack from mom.
Ah, we may be in shit here.
Oh, no.
I mean, she's killing her mobs.
That's good.
This is a mess.
Fuck!
I can't get hit by that.
That's just so stupid.
Come on.
Another one.
Oh,
come on, mom.
I'm ready.
I need to be the most patient man in the universe.
This is how I win this.
Fuck!
That's over.
I have no damage!
Bomb too late.
How the hell am I gonna do it faster?
Ah, I ended all.
Fuck!
I hate this challenge.
I feel useless, man.
I feel like I can't do nothing.
Fuck me.
Like, if I don't find some kind of active that does damage, I'm just cooked.
Give me that.
That was such a good run as well.
I had good HP, everything.
Damn it.
I need to beat this challenge.
Good damage there.
Useless item for me.
Let's try and go faster and faster.
Maybe that works.
In my favor, somehow.
I can see forever.
Sick.
D 'ah!
Open up your mouth!
Oh, he's not joking around.
Joey, Joey.
Dude!
Oh!
I mean, I'm getting rich here, so a shop that isn't just filled with that guy would be cool.
Right now.
Play it safe.
Pretty good.
Please be good.
That's not good.
This bandage is actually helping me quite a bit here.
I'm enjoying the bandage.
Good aim.
Eh, I'll do it.
Yeah, we got that back as well.
Ohoy.
I mean, we are not running out of utilities here.
I need my soul hearts!
Where are my soul hearts?
That was always such a cringy line from Daenerys Stormborn.
Or Dragonborn, whatever her name was, when she said soul hearts, you know?
And, uh, do I... do I... do I?
I do.
I do, indeed.
It's two of them!
Oh, shit!
Ah!
I think I'm in danger.
We kill this guy first, for sure.
The other one is not that scary right now.
He's just chilling.
Come on, red one.
He has some good damage.
Oh, that's nice.
Actually, huge.
Ohoy.
Ohoyoyoy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, good, good.
Man, I have good movement here.
Damn right, I was ready for that convert.
I was been ready for a long time.
Consolation prize?
Yeah, well, thanks.
I don't know if that does anything for me.
I'm gonna say no to that.
Probably not.
Show me some more good stuff here.
Need some good stuff.
Hmm.
No.
No, I'm wasting all my flies.
Ah, shit.
What is that?
Poop explosion destroyed.
Nah, I like finding bombs.
That is my other source of damage that I have, you know?
Arcade?
Ooh, I'm rich.
I could go for some arcade.
Yeah, sounds good.
I need to convert.
Come on, man.
Show me the good stuff.
Blue hearts.
Or black hearts.
I'll take both.
Also, demon meter is at zero.
Like, what's up with that?
How are we at zero?
Holy.
I think I'm up right now.
I've earned more than I've used.
I mean, I'm getting pretty lucky here.
Getting good items.
I'm also going to do this one.
More, more, more.
Uh, fully... oh, that could be pretty good, actually.
Depending on a couple things.
Let me donate some HP.
Oh, fuck.
I mean, okay.
Oh, my god.
Oh, shit.
No, it's a half one.
Ah, too bad.
Uh, no!
Ah, crap!
That's horrible.
Do I want this copy of a card pillow rune that was used?
I think it's fine.
We have 18 bombs.
We can survive without more bombs.
Now, secrets, though.
I think I see a secret.
But wait, do we currently have the... oh, Jackie!
You scared the crap out of me.
There we go.
Jackie is gonna give me a heart attack one of these days.
If I suddenly, you know, start to play bad, it's because I've died.
Because there's no way I can play bad if I'm alive.
Let's go.
That was the last drop of my coffee.
I'm gonna have to survive on that energy.
Sure, keep giving me money.
Hope I can use it on something.
Jackie, you cannot be on the table!
I put her on the bookshelf.
There's like a little spot on the bookshelf that she likes to hang out on, so I put her there.
She's nestled in between my books right now.
It's so cute.
Come here, son, come here.
You need to stop.
Okay, it's time to stop.
I don't know why I've heard that.
Jackie is at the microphone.
If you can hear Jackie, that's... if you can hear whatever's happening right now, it's Jackie!
Fine, I'm not... I'm just gonna leave her.
Jackie!
Fuck!
He's rubbing up against the microphone!
Jackie, stop!
No!
Okay, there we go.
She jumped down on her own.
Maybe that's all it takes, you know?
She had her fun and now she decided to leave on her own.
Dude, stop giving me money!
Oh, I didn't know that guy charged!
Oi!
Charge me!
Ah, of course you explode.
That's actually pretty good.
Uh, yeah, okay.
Where are my dragons?
Dog, get by ya.
But really, where are the blue hearts?
I found one.
The other one, I had like 10.
Nice.
Oh, he spawns them!
I see how it... I see, I see, I see, I see.
Okay, I missed that.
Two hearts right now.
I can't be dying on two hearts when I have like...
I don't even know how many.
That is horrible.
Please no.
Please no!
Man, this guy is shooting fast.
Duh, that's so good.
Very needed.
Nice.
I'm just gonna sit here.
Well, oh, finally a shop.
Spawn red, yes, yes!
That is so good.
But it's an active, so...
It's actually not good.
Uh,
wait, what?
Oh, yeah.
Right, chance to spawn the same item again.
I'll take that as well.
No.
Nope.
I need converter.
Oh, man.
What is that?
Call that a reward?
Where I'm from, that's called a slap in the face.
A bucket of cold water.
Okay, let's not die to this.
Actually massive.
Full health.
We're back.
Wait, is this mom?
This might be mom, actually.
So I'm not gonna go yet.
I have no idea where we are in the grand scheme of things.
Hi, mom.
No, please, man.
That's so mean.
Wait, why did she take us back here?
I guess she takes us back to the start.
It does make sense.
Probably not another one, right?
I'm starting to think that maybe we only have one secret room.
When we do challenges.
Or at least a higher chance of it.
Okay, so there is...
Oh, I thought there was only one hand.
But they just came down fast.
But there were two.
Oh, great.
We're done here.
Moving on.
Still can't believe my converter has been unused for so long.
It is a modern tragedy.
What
the...
Yeah, this one's gonna be rough.
Okay, it's time for you to die from bombs.
That's for you.
That didn't hit you?
Okay, there we go.
Yeah, bombs are the way.
Absolutely.
So hard!
Yeah, baby!
Oh, wait.
We're going back.
For the battery.
That's right.
In fact, I think I'm gonna grab this card instead.
Or the pill, I mean.
48 out of energy.
We're also gonna grab this.
We're gonna convert.
Haha, we're back!
Okay, we can't lose now.
Now we need...
What do we need?
We need more followers.
That's what we need.
Show me something good.
I feel like the further you get in a run, the more blue hearts spawn.
But that could just be me imagining things.
But definitely, like, if you go to heaven, you know?
There's more blue hearts there, for sure.
Because of all the blue fire.
But I think also hell.
Or shield, whatever.
Clean.
I'm getting pretty good with this guy, though, I will say.
Like these early stages, I'm getting done pretty consistently.
It's only later, when shit hits the fan.
Oh, I thought that guy would become my friend, though.
Time for bombs!
We got 23 bombs!
She pushed the bomb into me!
That's crazy.
Maybe you put bombs on the side instead, actually, like this.
There you go.
That's for you.
Oh my god.
Terrible.
There you go.
Man, they disappear so fast.
I need mom's...
I need mom's foot!
Shit!
I can't get damage in.
I don't know how to do it.
Dude, as soon as I'm watching for the fucking hand, it never comes!
Oh!
I'm so triggered right now.
Jackie, no!
Not in the middle of the combat!
I'm gonna bomb this.
It's all about the bombs.
We got three bombs left.
We need to make it count.
Come on!
Fuck!
I can't.
This challenge is fucking impossible.
You can't do nothing.
You have no damage.
You can't do shit.
It's fucking crazy.
Rage quit this piece of shit challenge.
Holy fuck, man.
It was the ultimate run as well.
You can't do damage!
It's so terrible.
And it's not even the end.
That's just the first boss, like the big one.
Man, no man.
I mean, converter would be the ultimate run if I also got some other items that helped me do damage, you know?
I know I don't have to do them in order, but I want to.
I want to do all the challenges, right?
There's a certain satisfaction from doing it in the right order.
A Seizel run is always good, because a Seizel is good, you know?
Like, what is going on with that?
I mean, I know there's not a right order, but there is an order from one and then down, right?
So there is an order, and I like following that, that's all.
Yeah, this one is crazy.
I'll do one last, but it's not going to be a challenge, because I've had it with the challenges.
I just had to bend a little bit there to you guys.
I just had to bend a little bit.
One more.
We're going to do random.
What's it going to be?
Okay, I like that, actually.
That's very different.
I'm happy about that.
He's going to do diagonal.
Oh, never mind, he's doing bombs.
I got to rewire my brain real quick here.
Oh, man!
I thought that bomb was going to come flying towards me there at the end.
And I got to jump.
And jump.
God, it feels good to shoot projectiles again.
I mean, it lets me get in here.
This is a great start.
I kind of want to go back and do the darkness challenge again now.
Just to cleanse my body after that.
Ah, look at this!
We got tinted rocks again.
I think we can confirm there's no tinted rocks and challenges.
Because there's just no way that I would have missed them all this time.
Bogo bombs.
All bomb pickups become... That is a synergy with what I have.
But do I want to become a bomb slinging bastard?
That's the question.
We need to ask ourselves.
Should I let the bombs into my heart?
Or do I reject them?
Nice.
Actually, we got to kill those little bottom dwellers here.
Otherwise, they keep spawning those guys.
Okay, so on this character, I think I need more hearts for sure.
But not too many.
Just a little bit, you know?
And then it's all about damage and familiars.
Whoa!
Good combo.
Oh, wait a minute.
Jage is at my feet.
One minute.
I gave her some early dinner.
She's also obsessed with something outside the window right now.
So much, in fact, that she didn't immediately go to the food, which was interesting.
Okay, this one's going to take a bit.
Oh, no way.
I can't afford those mistakes.
Nice.
Yeah, he's healing on those.
Actually, it's not that bad.
I keep thinking stats don't matter for me, but they do.
This is no longer the solar system.
Dude, damage matters, tears, and...
Oh, everything matters again.
Finding upgrades is going to feel good.
Okay, we're actually going to...
Oh, man.
Yeah, come on, then.
In fact, I think, theoretically, this character could be one of the characters that do the most damage, simply because you can pretty much double your damage at any time, right?
Assuming you hit with all your tiles.
Should I keep going in there?
I think so.
Cute pen.
Chance to fire a slowing shot.
That's nice.
I like slowing down people.
I will say the shops in this game are extremely underwhelming, compared to other roguelikes with shops, you know?
It's like the most underwhelming place to get items, in my opinion.
The most exciting being devils and angels, right?
Treasure rooms after that, then shops is pretty much the lowest of the low.
Great.
Thanks.
I don't trust myself.
I'm going to run into that fire.
So did he!
Makes me feel better.
I want to get to the flooded area, just because of the music and the ambiance.
I haven't seen it in 10 years.
That was kind of advanced dodging there.
A little bit risky, but it paid off.
I think we just go for it.
Still a treasure room missing.
Please HP, please HP, HP, HP.
Good.
Am I...
Oh, very nice.
Okay, that means I can pretty much take one of these.
Haha.
I sell my soul for money?
I don't think so.
Familia that fires spectral tears.
That's good for me.
So that means I can get four creatures when I use my active, right?
That's an active, so we don't want that.
I take this.
Let's go find the treasure room.
Oh, this is going to be so good.
I got five bombs as well.
I could go bomb some shit.
Let me check the other sides first.
See, there's rocks here, right?
So, imagine you were inside the secret room blowing up the wall.
You're not going to walk into a rock, so I know that's not a secret room.
Oh no, oh no.
I'm scared.
I'm actually gonna duplicate.
Look at that damage!
So many tears.
Ohoy!
The ultimate drive-by.
Here comes the train.
Beep, beep, beep.
Amazing.
It's not nice.
Treasure room should be, well, here.
And finding that little familiar is actually huge.
No way!
Walk into my shots.
I can't die here.
Okay, here we go.
Launches... oh no, it's an active.
I don't want it.
No.
Okay, that's good.
I'll give you a couple of bombs.
Why not?
Ha!
Didn't I also get other bomb effects on this guy?
Yeah, bop's curse.
I guess we embraced the bomb.
We let it into our hearts.
Maybe I shouldn't be gambling now.
Yeah, this is a bad idea.
Let's just blow some shit up.
Oh, nice.
We're gonna grab the eternal heart and get out.
This is a good start.
I could be looking for secrets.
Maybe here.
There we go.
How nice is that?
Yikes!
Super start!
Dude, let's kind of do a speed run here.
Like, semi-speed run.
We're not gonna go super hard, but we're gonna go hard, you know?
Here we go.
I could go in there, but I'm not gonna.
I don't know what just happened.
Why not?
I'll bite.
Hey, okay.
Slow, slow, slow, and then go the other way.
Look at that stutter step.
Advanced strategies here.
That's pretty good, huh?
Hey, actually.
That was scary.
What is that?
Dude, how do you dodge that?
Spider baby.
What does that actually do?
Sucks.
I need a converter.
That's what's gonna save this even more.
Ah, then again, then I can't use my little box, actually.
Maybe it's not the best in this case.
Ah, this is not the one.
This is the shitty one.
Dude, don't be fooled.
Not like last time.
Oh, I could donate some money, I guess.
Why, you know what?
Why not?
Throw it all in there.
We got to start donating to that.
I want to see what happens when we get to 500.
Maybe even a thousand.
Who knows?
Speaking of donations, we should do greed again and donate to the donation machine at the end.
That definitely unlocked a lot of shit last time.
Okay.
I will say, though, I need more health.
I'm once again asking for more health.
I'm gonna go in.
I feel it.
I'm gonna duplicate and go nuts.
He's gonna charge me at some point.
There he comes.
Oh, god.
Oh, god, man!
Yes!
Oh, everything is aligning here.
It's wonderful.
We got good damage.
We got health.
What am I looking for now?
No actives.
I guess more tear damage and, you know, just straight up stats.
Because that's gonna boost my guys.
Not boosting the boys.
Dodge it.
Oh, man.
Okay.
If these guys were the ones that jumped on top of me, I would have been dead here.
I'm not gonna take the chance on that.
You hurt me, I take health back.
Ah, I'm not gonna go in there.
Even with one coin.
Weird room.
Okay, fine.
Hey, okay!
Nice to be winning here.
Come on, then.
Steam sale.
Wait, what is that last guy I have with me?
Ghost baby.
Wait, we have two?
One is from when I start.
Then we got another one from here.
What's the last one?
What is doing that?
I... I don't know.
One of these is a... a stowaway.
I don't know where you're coming from.
Weird.
Maybe it's something that happens on this character when...
when you just keep going on, you know?
You get more followers.
Maybe on a certain floor you get more followers.
Dude, how is this happening?
Kill him.
I may actually just die right now.
Okay, at least they die fast.
At least I'm healing.
I'm done.
Rage quit!
Fuck this, man.
My brain is mush at this point.
I can't even play properly.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
How is this game just getting harder and harder somehow?
I don't understand.
It's either that or I'm getting worse.
Maybe both.
Oh, I forgot about Bethany.
That's true.
Next time, I'm gonna write it down.
Uh, remember Bethany?
She's calling.
There we go.
I wrote it down.
Killing Hush on first attempt is huge, though.
Right, I did that.
I totally forgot.
My victory was overshadowed by a massive chain of failures.
And I actually completely forgot about that run.
You're right.
That did happen.
That was cool.
And then I started playing the solar system and it was not a good time.
Well, it was a good time until it wasn't.
Everything is terrible.
The games just got harder.
Yeah, right?
I'm not crazy.
It is getting harder.
Any thoughts on lore?
Yeah, Isaac is having some trouble.
This guy's gonna have PTSD when he grows up, if he grows up.
It wouldn't even surprise me if he... if everything we're going through is like some PTSD induced nightmare that isn't even real, you know?
Like, he's in that box right now, crying, thinking about all this.
And he's just imagining the worst.
I mean, this game is dark when it comes to the lore.
Like, where it almost makes me uncomfortable, you know?
To think about.
I couldn't even imagine something like that.
But that stuff exists in real life.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Unlocked a new ending with that.
True.
Another one.
The game never does end, truly.
I think I've seen, I don't even know, 20 different credits at this point.
I wonder if there's a real credits.
Yeah, the end is never the end.
I mean, listen.
It's okay to rage sometimes.
It's a difficult game, you know?
And it's somewhat reliant on RNG as well at times, you know?
The game can fuck you.
The game giveth and it taketh away.
It happens.
It doesn't mean I'm not gonna play Isaac anymore, don't worry about it.
If anything, it's getting more personal.
I wanna beat this.
I wanna get in there in that win, guys.
I'm not giving up on the solar system.
It shall be beaten.
I just need the right items, you know?
And I need the right environment and mental situation and everything.
When all of that aligns, just like the planets, good things will happen.
Hahaha, solar system is bullshit.
It is.
But imagine the euphoria when I beat it, though.
Like, it's gonna be so worth it for when that happens.
I can already see it coming, you know?
It's gonna be so good.
The feeling is gonna be immense.
Also, for those that didn't see it when we started the stream, I'm gonna show it again, because I'm so proud of this.
Oh wait, you can't see it.
Now you can see it.
This is the backlog, the new one improved.
And if you go through these, you can check, you know, what's on the backlog, what's played, what I'm currently playing.
And stuff like that, you know?
Search functions.
It's updated immediately.
You can actually search now.
It's a whole thing.
You guys are gonna love it, I think.
It's gonna be so good.
We're gonna link to it in the Discord, so we don't have the same requests for games all the time.
Yeah, it's not live yet, but probably very soon.
I'm just testing it, you know?
There's still some things that aren't working and all that.
Do you have SimCity 2000 in the backlog?
I don't think so.
I gotta be honest, I make some of those games up in my mind.
I've played a bunch of them, but I don't remember if I've played that exact one.
Did you make the site?
Well, you know, I coded it with AI.
Or at least with help from AI.
You can't really do it all with AI.
You gotta do something yourself.
But it's pretty much Claude, you know?
It's not up yet.
It's just local right now.
I'm just testing things.
I'm trying to fix a couple things that aren't working, but mostly it's working.
I am a programmer, yes.
I guess you technically could make it solely with AI if you really want it.
But I don't know, man.
That doesn't sound...
I mean, I feel like you gotta know what to tell the AI what you need, right?
At least.
Especially in terms of security and all that.
Not that this website is gonna, you know, contain any super special sauce secrets that are gonna be problematic if they leak.
But you know my point.
The squatters in my VPS.
What is VPS?
You mean, VPM?
Exactly.
You need to have a general idea of how to get started, right?
Don't worry, there's no data mining in this.
I've checked the code.
It's all good.
You need to know frameworks.
Yeah, yeah.
And some idea of what you want, right?
Like, this took a long time.
I've been spending a lot of hours on this so far.
But you know what?
I enjoy it.
I love doing that stuff.
Oh, virtual private server.
Right, okay.
Well, I'm not really, like, a front-end or back-end type guy at all.
Like, I'm mostly...
I've been doing Python, you know?
That's sort of my thing.
Mostly data science.
But honestly, data science is kind of dying because of AI.
It's not really a job that's gonna exist for much longer.
But it's kind of interesting to get into the whole...
or learning about how to set up websites or code up bots for Discord and stuff like that.
You know, you learn a lot from it, and it's really cool.
You think you can beat Hush without SciFly if you remember his tactics?
Of course.
It's like saying, hey, do you think you can beat this boss if you're good enough?
Yeah, if I'm good enough.
If you're trying to say the SciFly carried me, I'm gonna say...
probably.
The game is about items that carry you, right?
I use AI.
I use Claude, I mean.
I think chatgbt5.5 just came out and people are praising it, but I don't know.
I haven't tried it yet.
Apparently, it's better at some things.
But I enjoy Claude.
And VS Code.
I heard that... what's it called?
What's that other app?
That's very popular these days.
It's not VS Code, but it's like the agentic one.
I forgot the name of it, but apparently they're rolling out a whole new version of it where it's actually the whole new programming paradigm.
Yeah, cursor.
So, the new cursor, it's like set up from the ground up to be running multiple agents, you know?
You're like this guy that just is commanding this army of coders.
It's gonna be the future, you know?
Like, there's no way around it.
It's just crazy to think about that you're sitting there with like five prompts and you have five different AIs doing five different things at the same time.
You're just delegating out tasks, you know?
Hot take, AI bad.
I think it is a hot take.
I think any programmer nowadays, if you don't get into AI right now, you're gonna have trouble finding a job.
Because it's just too damn good.
One of my friends who's, you know, running a company right now in Copenhagen, he says if people are applying for a job there and they say they don't use AI, they're just not gonna get a job at all.
They're not even gonna give them a chance.
Because it is just like shooting yourself in the foot.
You know?
It's easily 10X-ing everyone who's programming.
A general sentiment on the internet seems to be anti-AI.
Yeah, if you're hanging out on X all day, or Reddit or something.
Actual people with actual jobs are using AI.
And if you don't, you're gonna lose your job pretty soon.
It depends what kind of AI you're talking about as well.
I mean, you know, saying AI is kind of vague.
It's too vague, in my opinion.
It's like you're saying generative AI is what sucks.
That's also, you know, vague.
Because technically, you know, coding agents are generative, if you think about it.
If you're talking about art or music, then that's different, right?
Exactly.
So, careful not to throw around too many vague things, you know?
It's muddying the waters.
I use plot code as a VS code extension, yes.
It is the VS code extension, plot code.
I don't use the one in the terminal.
Although I haven't tried it, but...
Yeah, it's like, you know, freaking motors took over the people's jobs that were controlling the elevators back in the day, you know?
That sounds like a shit job.
I'm back.
How was the Unity run?
We're doing a speed run in Unity, guys.
We're making a 3D model of Yulith.
Now, Yulith went okay until I started playing really bad.
That was definitely on me.
I think I was a little tilted from playing with the solar system, and that led over into Yulith a little bit.
Now,
what AI to raise my kids?
I mean, it's probably gonna be a thing.
And not too long, you know?
It is happening.
It's crazy.
I can barely keep up with everything that's going on with AI and everything else in tech right now.
I feel like every other year, or maybe every year, we get even smaller chips, you know?
What are we down to now?
Almost one nanometer, I think?
I think it's one or two nanometers right now.
It's unbelievable.
I still can't believe you one-shot a hush.
I almost can't believe it either.
Actually, I can.
I was playing as Azul.
He's my boy.
We're at two nanometers?
Yeah.
And now we're starting to stack those wafers vertically as well.
I don't want smaller chips.
I want to be able to taste the oil and salt.
What about vinegar?
Are you a vinegar chips man?
It's nothing like it, man.
If you get the good vinegar chips and some beer.
A nice IPA.
8%.
Oof.
That combo.
Ooh!
I kind of want to do that.
I should get that tonight.
Nah.
Yeah, I should.
I should.
Number one is Azul Glazer.
I admit it.
I love him.
AI kind of took the fun out of software engineering for you.
That's crazy because it put the fun into it for me even more.
Like I loved coding before that.
Now I love it even more.
It's like I have this idea.
I can, instead of getting it done in a week, I can get it done in like an hour.
It's that crazy.
It's super good for prototyping, but that's just my opinion.
I feel like I can try out more things, you know?
The best way I can put it is imagine you're in World of Warcraft.
And you want to try out different specs.
Before AI, you could only level up with one spec and you could never respec.
Now I can respec whenever I want and try out different builds.
You know what I mean?
It's good for prototyping, but if you want to make something really deep and actually like performative and... I mean, I'm talking about stuff not just like a game website that tracks what you've played, right?
Because that's super simple if you think about it.
Obviously, you got to get in the trenches right now, but pretty soon you probably won't have to do that.
It's improving at such an insane rate, you know?
Yeah, it's definitely easier to get into new stuff.
Yeah, that's it.
Or if you want to learn a new language.
You know, I didn't know anything about Swelter or I didn't even use any JavaScript.
But now that I'm doing this, I can learn all that.
And it's actually a lot of fun, but that is just me, you know?
You can disagree with that.
Oh man, it's over.
Yeah, a lot of jobs, Rip.
I can't believe Jackie didn't jump up since I put her down again.
I guess feeding her did the trick there.
I guess she was especially hungry today.
I usually feed her at seven.
Wait, you were at your dog's birthday party?
You have birthday?
Put her down!
I didn't mean that out of the way.
I didn't mean that.
You know what I meant.
Wait, you actually hold or held a birthday party for your dog?
That's awesome.
Did you make a cake out of kibble and then put a little hat on her or something?
That's amazing.
She had presents and cake.
That is so nice.
Your dog is out there having better birthdays than some people out there, you know?
Amazing.
That's so cute.
When it was Jackie's birthday, I gave her some dry food with some wet food and then some snacks sprinkled on top.
And then I gave her some toys.
That was my present to her.
Have you ever thought about thinking?
I guess so.
Cool, cool.
I mean, if you think about it, it is kind of crazy to think.
Will your side have a request button?
I was thinking about that, but then I thought, oh man, maybe it's not a good idea to give people an opportunity to...
I don't know.
I'm thinking of the Finnish border right now, pretty much, you know?
And could we have something like that going on with the site?
But, I mean, yeah, you could definitely have like a request, put it in a queue, and then I can look at the queue and go like accept or not, and it gets put on, you know?
But, I mean, it's not really a big deal.
People recommend games to me.
That's cool.
And I just added, you know, it's not a big deal.
The biggest thing it's gonna solve is just...
It's gonna be easier for people to check what's out there and what they can watch and what is on the backlog.
What games I've already played and stuff like that.
And it's also gonna double as a website that shows my ranking, so to speak.
Here, I'm gonna show it again.
So if you look at it, you can see there's like numbers on it.
These are just some quick numbers I put in.
But ideally, I want this to be my...
My, what do you call it?
Tieralist, right?
But a better version of it.
So you can sort by rating here, you know?
Instead of by A to Z.
So that's a way to just check, you know, what rating I gave a game.
But it's not really a rating.
It's more like how much did I enjoy playing that game, you know?
And that can be colored by my situation in life at the moment, you know?
All was really in a bad state.
So that's why I really enjoyed this game at the time.
It's not an objective, you know, rating on a game.
It's my personal...
How much did I enjoy playing it, right?
Maybe link it with Discord for requests.
Yeah, we could do that.
Most requested game is probably...
Oh, that's a good question.
I would say maybe Red Dead Redemption.
The Last of Us 2 9.9s out of 10 is based.
Is it?
It's a very critically acclaimed game.
Like, it's probably one of the best single-player games ever made.
Don't people only request-
Red Dead Redemption 2?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
I mean, I would imagine people would want me to play the first game first.
Right?
Loud minority hates it.
That's fine.
People can hate it.
I love it.
We don't have to have the same opinion, right?
I also, when I did this, it reminded me what other games I've been playing and not putting out because I didn't enjoy them.
And there's still a couple I don't remember because they just face out of my mind.
But like Sea of Thieves, I tried briefly to record and it just wasn't for me, you know?
So I never put that out.
Outer Worlds?
Really didn't like that game either.
I was thinking of recording Stormgate, but it being like a multiplayer game and it was also early access.
I was super sold because it was all the old people behind Starcraft 2 who was making it, you know?
I was super hyped about it.
Didn't really turn out to be that great yet.
Who knows?
Maybe it'll be better.
But yeah.
Terraria 0?
Nah, it doesn't deserve a 0.
I put it at 5.
It's like halfway marked, right?
A game would have to be like extremely bad to be at 0 out of 10.
I hate Outer Worlds, yes.
What about that Golem game?
Wait, what Golem game?
Golem game?
Have I played a Golem game?
Saldainen Golem sign.
Oh, Golem!
I haven't played it, but I heard it's terrible.
I heard it's absolutely terrible.
I mean, it would be fun to play, you know, and then just take on it, you know?
See how bad it actually is.
Because sometimes people are wrong.
I mean, who knows?
Maybe it's a banger and people don't know what they're talking about.
So bad it's good.
What if I played and I actually like it?
Is that going to be rage bait?
I'd respect it.
I mean, of course, thank you.
I'd respect any game you like or dislike.
So yeah, thanks.
I've not played Ark Survival.
If you pretend to like it, it would be a great bit.
Oh, that's actually... giving me ideas now.
Let me think.
You know what would be funny, actually?
Imagine if I actually had played Isaac before.
For example, right?
Let's say I was literally one of the best people in the world at Isaac.
Like I was a world champion, but nobody knew.
And I would I would do the classic thing of, you know, what's it called?
Hustling, right?
Where you pretend to be bad at pool or something, and then you take their money.
So imagine that I was pretending to play bad for like, I don't know, a week or so.
And then I switch over, you know, and I just suddenly start beating world records.
Wouldn't that be the funniest content of all time?
I mean, obviously, I would come clean about it afterwards, but wouldn't that be really funny?
I feel like someone should try to do that out there.
Holy shit.
That would be so good.
Oh, man.
I'm sorry, we're pretty sure you're not pretending.
I'm that bad, huh?
Come on.
Who knows?
Maybe I'm just really good actor.
You don't know, joy baiting.
I like that.
We should normalize joy baiting.
I like that term.
Best actor in the world.
I mean, I have I have my moments in this game, right?
And you make a documentary about it and get millions of views.
Yeah, something like that.
I watched the video on YouTube where someone was hiring like a coach on Fiverr, I think, to teach them how to play Counter Strike, you know?
But they were actually like a pro.
And I thought that video was so fun.
Something like that is what I mean, you know?
Have you seen those videos?
I love watching those.
I think it's super fun.
I mean, as long as it's all in good fun, right?
And you're not making people angry with it.
You've seen them with League of Legends?
Okay.
Please joy bait next stream.
How would I be joy baiting?
What would that entail?
Joy baiting.
How would you joy bait?
I know how you would joy bait.
You would go, guys, we're having a stream every day for the next week.
Five hour streams every day and cooking streams every day after that.
And then I just lie.
It doesn't happen.
We're just gonna play Solar System all week.
I mean, that would be a joy bait turned into a rage bait, maybe.
Or a sad bait.
I feel like if you pretended to be bad at a game, eventually you'd let it slip by using a turn, only the community knows.
Good point.
Yeah, I mean, sometimes it's hard to control what you're saying when you're playing a game and talking out loud, you know?
That's a good point, actually.
That's worse than rage bait.
That's how you destroy your character.
I mean, of course, it's not a good thing to just be straight up lying, you know.
Hey, I'm gonna stream next week and then just not do it and go, ha ha, you got joy baited.
That's so stupid.
Like, that is the dumbest thing of all time.
No, it does not need to be a thing.
I have tried Noita.
It's a great game.
It's on my channel.
You can check it out there.
I am gonna do another Minecraft season.
With mods.
I don't know when, though.
I'm still, like, on a cooldown period after the last season.
So I'm waiting to be in the right mindset to go, yeah, it's time for Minecraft again.
Did you like Hush?
I did like Hush.
I'm gonna predict right now, and maybe this is the one time where I reveal, or let it slip that I'm actually a... finding a Vysek pro.
I predict there's going to be a boss called Hush Hush.
That's even more powerful.
If I'm right about that, that will seem so unbelievable.
Oh, Hush Hush?
Why Hush Hush?
It's Hush, isn't it?
How does he know?
I'm just that good, man.
You guys are actually so easy to read.
I know that there's no boss named that, just based on your responses.
You can't fool me.
I'm an expert at reading you guys in chat.
I really am.
Like, I can tell.
You can... I don't know how I can tell.
I can just tell.
Ask me to ask you any question.
No, ask me... No, wait, how does it work?
I will ask you... No, wait.
Huh.
I don't... Ask me to make a prediction about something, okay?
In anything.
And I will prove to you that I can gauge your response.
That doesn't even make any sense.
I don't know where I'm going with this.
I need to shut off the stream.
I can't even think.
Predict how many characters there are.
Oh, okay.
Wait, I'm trying to think.
One, two, three, four...
I think... 22 characters.
And now respond without spoiling.
And I can tell.
Wait a minute, okay.
You can't just write lol.
That's cheating.
Okay, but based on the first couple of people, I would say I was wrong.
There's not 22.
But then again, I'm also drawing on some prior knowledge here, which is statistics.
Just statistically speaking, there's a very low chance I'm right.
You know?
Yeah, I can tell when you guys are joking.
Like, it's so easy.
You think you got me, but you don't.
Okay, Mr. Peanut Bumpter.
I guess you're right.
There's actually 22.7.
Wow, you can't say that in 2026, bro.
How dare you?
You actually have unlocked everything?
No, I haven't.
Dude, next time, I'm gonna write this on my list.
We're gonna check the items again.
I want to see how many I got.
Check item list next time.
That should be fun.
I'm gonna make a prediction before I check, and I promise not to check beforehand, obviously.
Otherwise, it's no fun.
So you gotta trust me on that.
I'm gonna predict how many items I have found, and we'll see how close I am, okay?
Make a prediction now.
Okay, there are 680 items.
No, no, no, wait.
430.
That's my final prediction.
Achievements would spoil it, then I'm not gonna look at achievements.
We're gonna check next time.
How did he get us both?
Come on, it's too easy.
It's too easy.
All right, I'm out of here, guys.
I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna go chill with my cat.
I'm gonna make some food.
I'm gonna hang out with my cat.
That's all I have.
And you guys, thanks for being here watching me and chatting.
It's good to talk to you.
Anyway, uh, new game on the channel soon.
You probably sussed it out.
I was being pretty obvious with it.
So yeah, so far I'm enjoying it.
I think I can confidently put it up even without finishing it.
This one is a banger.
Yeah, I'll see ya.
Bye-bye.